<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>


<home>
	<content>
		<title>Day Cafe'</title>
		<home>Home</home>
		<about>About</about>
		<Coffees>Coffees</Coffees>
		<Blog>Blog</Blog>
		<Contact>Contact</Contact>
		<logIn>Login</logIn>
		<title1>Day Cafe'</title1>
		<content1>Tasty Of  Day Cafe'</content1>
		<content2>The Cafe That brings delightful to your day</content2>
		<about_bt>About Us</about_bt>
		<reservation_bt>Make a Reservation</reservation_bt>
		<offer>OUR Coffee OFFER</offer>
		<types1>TYPES OF COFFEE</types1>
		<types2>BEAN VARIETIES</types2>
		<types3>COFFEE and PASTRY</types3>
		<types4>COFFEE TO GO</types4>
		<types_text>looking at its layout. The point of</types_text>
		<read_bt>Read More</read_bt>
		<about2>About Our shop</about2>
		<about3>What says customers</about3>
		<client>Joy and Angelica</client>
		<info>"Sobrang sarap ng coffee nila dito and na enjoy namin yung place together, perfect place para mag review or tumambay" </info>
		<client1>Wilson</client1>
		<info1> "Gustong gusto ko ang mga coffee/ drinks nila dito at saka yung pastry panalo kaya babalik balikan mo talaga"</info1>
		<client2>Daniela</client2>
		<info2>"Perfect to sa katulad ko na single itong coffee shop na ito, hindi ko na kailangan ng ka cuddle,kape lang ng "Days Cafe"sapat na"</info2>
		<date>05 April</date>
		<barista1>Robert Chua "Store Manager"</barista1>
		<barista2>Tony Pacheco "Head Barista" and his crew mate </barista2>
		<blog> Our Boss and Crews</blog>
		<send> SEND </send>
		<copy>Sample Website Only</copy>
		<touch>Get in Touch</touch>
		<text1>
			Robert Chua was in the middle of brewing a cup of coffee for himself, when he thought of opening a coffee shop outside their house. Though he is not a pro-barista, he truly is passionate in making and drinking coffee. Plus, he had always dreamed of opening his own coffee shop. So, he quickly grabbed a small table and his home coffee equipment, offering coffee at the mini-mart their family had also just opened this year.
		</text1>
        <text2>
        	"There is no one secret to a successful coffee shop; in fact, most secrets in business boil down to either hard work, extensive experience, or luck or a combination of all three.I worked as "Barista" in more than fifteen coffee shops with varying degrees of success"--Tony "Head Barista"
        </text2>

	






	</content>
</home>

